SANTHES THIRAVIYA RAJA J

Full Stack Developer

+91 94897 89332

santhes2013@gmail.com

santhes-raja.github.io

Chennai



SUMMARY

A self-motivated IT professional with strong knowledge and proficiency in Full Stack Web development in HTML5, CSS3, PHP, Laravel, Angular 2+, Angular 1.x, MySQL, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Typescript. Bringing along with 4+ Years of technical work experience in high end web development for leading clients.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

RDO India Pvt Ltd.

11/2016 - Present CI

RDO's technology has been built by lawyers, mediators and arbitrators from around the world who understand the need for greater access to justice and dispute resolution because they have experienced it themselves.

Junior Software Engineer

Eagle Software India Pvt Ltd

10/2014-11/2016 Chennai

Eagle Software India Pvt Ltd. forms an integral part of the renowned Eagle Corporate Group. Eagle Corporate group is known for its 50 years of diversified business interactions comprising significant global market share in printing technology and security related solutions.

EDUCATION

B.E Electronics & Communication

PET Engineering College

CGPA

6.5 / 10

2009 - 2013 Vallioor

Higher Secondary

Govt. High School

2007 - 2009 Vallioor

%

85 / 100

SSLC

St. Aloysius High School

2006-2007 Vallioor

%

60.8 / 100

SKILLS

HTML5	CSS3 Ar	ngular 2+	+
Angular Js	1.x Boots	strap	 JavaScript
jQuery	Typescript	PHP	-
Laravel 5+	MySQL	NPM	Node
Git Visu	ıal Studio C	ode	
Sublime Te	ext Phpst	orm I	ES5 ES6

LANGUAGES

Tamil Native	••••	
English	••••	
Proficient		

FIND MEONLINE

Linked in

https://in.linkedin.com/in/santhes-thiraviya-raja-j-55323178

Git Hub

https://santhes-raja.github.io

PROJECTS

RDO v2.0

02/2019 - Ongoing Chennai https://rdov2.resolvedisputes.online

Technology: Laravel 5.7, PHP, MySQL, HTML 5, CSS 3, Ant Design, Angular 7, Typescript

• This is a web-based case management system, which is an upgraded version of RDO.

RDO Web

10/2018 – 11/2018 Chennai https://resolvedisputes.online

Technology: PHP, HTML 5, CSS 3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery

RDO is simple to use dispute resolution technology which has been built by dispute resolution practitioners who understand the process. RDO technology is designed with the purpose of making dispute resolution as effortless and as effective as possible.

- This is a website design of RDO (Resolve Disputes Online).
- This website works with customer demo request and application features.

SMC v1.0

2018 Singapore

https://smc.resolvedisputes.online

Technology: Laravel 5.5, PHP, MySQL, HTML 5, CSS 3, Bootstrap, AngularJS 1.X, JavaScript, jQuery, WebRTC, Socket.io

- This is a web-based case management system, which is an online dispute resolution-based application which is widely used in legal industries in Singapore.
- This application works with Group of mediators to settle the dispute between parties.
- This application is RDO first Client in Singapore.
- SMC means Singapore Mediation Center.

RDO v1.0

2016 - 2017 Chennai

https://demo.resolvedisputes.online

Technology: Laravel 5.5, PHP, MySQL, HTML 5, CSS 3, Bootstrap, AngularJS 1.X, JavaScript, jQuery, WebRTC, Socket.io

- This is a web-based case management system, which is an online dispute resolution-based application which is widely used in legal industries in Singapore and UK.
- This application works with Group of mediators and arbitrators to settle the dispute between parties.
- Communication based modules like Text Chat, Audio / Video Chat using WebRTC and Post and settlement agreement module.
- Single User can have multiple cases in the same dashboard.
- Same User can be as claimant in 1 case and respondent in another case. Lawyers can also login to support their parties in settling their cases.
- File & Documents Module and Appointments (calendar) module adds more strength to this Case Management System.

Ticketreel (Online Movie Ticket Booking System)

2014 – 2015 Chennai https://ticketreel.com

Technology: PHP, MySQL, HTML 5, CSS 3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, XML, SOAP API

Ticketreel is Online movie ticket booking application. This system Administration to easily update all theatre details, prices, pictures, movies details and other information online.

- Manage Theatre
- Manage Settings
- Movie Reviews & Rating
- · Manage categories and movies.
- Manage Movies options.
- · Advanced pricing algorithms
- · Booking Order and Booking.
- Take payments online using CC Avenue and Pay U Money payment gateways.
- Automatic email and SMS notification of bookings.
- Fast and friendly quick search and advanced search features.
- Live ticketing system with theatre and web.

Digital Account Opening Application (TMB)

2016 Chennai

Technology: PHP, Oracle, HTML 5, CSS 3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax

- Account Opening Digital Application is simple to create a bank account by this application internal purpose.
- This is a web-based system, which is used by bank employees internal to opening new account via this application.
- · Three Types of Operations.
 - 1. Branches upload a document filled by the customers directly scanning using the application.
 - 2. The Data Entry Operators can enter the data by seeing the document copy and submit data.
 - 3. Once Data Entry completes, the supervisor of the data entry operators verifying the document and approved to open account via Finacle.

PERSONAL DOSSIER

Gender: Male

Nationality: Indian

Permanent Address: #58, Middle Street, Chembadu, Vallioor – 627117

Mobile: +91 94897 89332

Thanks,

Santhes Thiraviya Raja J